

NIKOLAAS DAEM

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Confident, highly organised and passionate about developing software. Keen on learning and expanding my knowledge in various fields within the IT industry. Bringing forth several years of experience in a lead position at youth movements and work fields.

EDUCATION

Java Developer IOT

© INTEC BRUSSEL

PROJECTS

https://github.com/DaemNE

LANGUAGES

CONTACT

- Ŷ
- ☑ NikolaasDaem@hotmail.com
- **C**
- in /nikolaasdaem

IT-SKILLS

- Proficiënt in / with : Java, Python, SQL & MYSQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Spring, JDBC,
- Software: Excel, Word

SKILLS

- Exceptional communication and networking skills
- Successful working in a team environment, as well as independently
- The ability to work under pressure and multi-task
- Listening and following instructions and deliver quality results
- Not afraid to ask for help when stuck

WORK EXPERIENCE

Environment Brussel., Events Assistant

FEB 2020 - FEB 2021

- Organized and supported multiple events
- Constantly updated the company's policies concerning the corona virus
- Monitored the agenda of our rooms to rent
- S.P.O.C. for our clients and our partners

McDonalds., Versatile employee

2018 - 2019

Versatile tasks

Private tutoring - Dutch classes

2018 - 2019

Tutored children of ages 6-10

EXTRA-CURRICULAR

CHIRO Schaarbeek., Managing Leader

2019 - NOW

CHIRO Ganshoren., Member + Leader

2003 - 2018